EMERGENCIES
紧急情况
Give me a sedative.
给我一剂镇静剂。
What do we do ?
我们做什么 ？
- Calm down, wait. - My mother is not well.
- 冷静，等等。 - 我妈妈身体不太好。
How long ?
多久 ？
She didn't sleep all night.
她一夜没睡。
We'll take care of her, just wait a bit.
我们会照顾她的，稍等一下。
Let it pass.
让它过去吧。
Doctor, please...
医生，请...
Clear the way!
开道！
Stay with me. Keep your eyes open!
留在我身边。睁大你的眼睛！
- THANKS. - You are welcome.
- 谢谢。 - 不客气。
Maman.
妈妈。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
THE HUNT IN THE BLOOD
血中狩猎
- Mr. An Mun-ju? - Yes.
- 安文柱先生？ - 是的。
Fortunately, the nerves are intact.
幸运的是，神经完好无损。
An operation for the scar?
疤痕需要手术吗？
We closed the wound,
我们缝合了伤口，
but you have to have surgery quickly, or it might show.
但你必须尽快进行手术， 否则可能会出现。
It's expensive, no ?
很贵，不是吗？
I know a specialist.
我认识一位专家。
Here, look. This is a recent operation.
在这里，看。 这是最近的一次手术。
- Do you see the scar on his forehead? - Yes.
- 你看到他额头上的伤疤了吗？ - 是的。
That was before the laser surgery.
那是在激光手术之前。
This is the result afterwards.
这是后来的结果。
I see.
我懂了。
A scar on your face, at your age.
在你这个年纪，脸上有疤痕。
It would be better to have surgery.
最好做手术。
No it'll be fine. THANKS.
不，会没事的。谢谢。
Choi Han-seon?
崔汉善？
Come in.
进来。
Woo-jin.
宇进.
How are you ?
你好吗 ？
Show me.
给我看看。
Non.
非。
Whore !
妓女！
How many points?
多少分？
Thirty.
三十。
Damn, bastards. It pisses me off.
该死的，混蛋们。它气死我了。
It should be reported.
应该报告。
Notify the police and your mother will be there.
通知警察，你妈妈就会在那里。
- I can't. - For what ?
- 我不能。 - 为了什么 ？
It would put my mother in danger.
这会让我的母亲陷入危险。
Damn, seriously?
该死，认真的吗？
And if not, the contract?
如果没有，合同呢？
So look.
所以看。
I have never seen that. “Loan Extension Fees”.
我从来没有见过这样的情况。 “贷款延期费”。
You pay 10% of the capital every week until you repay the loan.
您每周支付 10% 的资本 ，直到偿还贷款。
Your mother borrowed 50 million, so five million in fees.
你妈妈借了5000万， 所以费用是500万。
And if you miss the deadline, it doubles.
如果你错过了最后期限，费用会加倍。
The interest rate increases from 5% to 20%.
利率从5%增加到20%。
They wrote it in the fine print, the bastards.
他们把它写 在精美的印刷品上，混蛋。
A scam. Your mother couldn't have known that.
一个骗局。 你妈妈不可能知道这一点。
What do I do ?
我该怎么办 ？
Pay them back immediately.
立即还钱给他们。
If the interest goes up, they'll seize your house.
如果利息上涨， 他们就会没收你的房子。
We don't have the money.
我们没有钱。
Damn, piss off.
妈的，滚蛋吧。
Let's go to lunch.
我们去吃午饭吧。
What do you want ? I invite you.
你想要什么 ？我邀请你。
He has steak.
他有牛排。
You haven't lost your sense of humor.
你并没有失去幽默感。
Really, steak.
真的，牛排。
Bon.
邦。
How do you like sautéed pork? It's worth a steak.
你喜欢炒猪肉吗？ 值得吃一块牛排。
All right.
好的。
I come here after training.
我训练结束后就来到这里。
I have my little routine.
我有我的小习惯。
Don't say anything and enjoy, understand?
什么也不说，享受，明白吗？
- Understood. - Hi !
- 明白了。 - 你好 ！
Happy to see you.
高兴看到你。
- Wow ! - We are two.
- 哇 ！ - 我们是两个人。
A new friend ?
一个新朋友 ？
- Good morning. - A boxer friend.
- 早上好。 - 一位拳击手朋友。
Really ?
真的 ？
I have to answer.
我必须回答。
Hello, this is Woo-jin. How are you ?
大家好，我是宇珍。你好吗 ？
I wanted to talk to you...
我想和你谈谈...
GUN-WOO
建宇
Yes, Gun-woo?
是的，建宇？
Woo-jin read the contract.
宇镇读了合同。
They are professional scammers. We got screwed.
他们是职业骗子。 我们被搞砸了。
It's not your fault.
这不是你的错。
Thank you honey.
谢谢亲爱的。
What did they say about your cheek?
他们对你的脸颊说了什么？
It heals well.
痊愈得很好。
What a relief!
真是如释重负！
I'll clean the cafe with Woo-Jin.
我会和宇进一起打扫咖啡馆。
Stay home and rest.
呆在家里休息。
No, I'm going to clean up. Do not worry.
不，我要去打扫。不用担心。
It's nothing, I'll take care of it when I get home.
没什么，我回家后会处理的。
It's ready !
准备好了 ！
I call you later.
我一会儿给你打电话。
- Okay. - See you later.
- 好的。 - 稍后见。
Come on, help me out on this one.
来吧，帮我解决一下这个问题。
It's for a friend, not for me.
这是给朋友的，不是给我的。
I will reimburse you on time.
我会按时偿还你的。
Everything will be fine.
一切都会好起来的。
2% interest? Might as well go to the bank.
2%利息？还是去银行吧。
Do it to me at 1%. I beg you. Just this once.
就按1%给我做吧。 我求求你。就这一次。
He's a very good friend.
他是一个非常好的朋友。
Help me out.
帮帮我。
I collected a lot of money for you
我为你收集了很多钱
and I never asked you anything.
我从来没有问过你任何事情。
You had to call me.
你必须给我打电话。
She just brought it.
她刚带来的。
Taste.
品尝。
The best pork stir-fry in the country.
国内最好吃的炒猪肉。
SO ? Enjoy your food.
所以 ？享受你的食物。
GO TO THE OFFICE, WE’RE GOING TO CHAT
去办公室，我们要聊聊
He's angry, so don't get into trouble.
他很生气， 所以不要惹上麻烦。
Let me talk.
让我说。
All right.
好的。
- Mr. Seo? - Yes ?
- 徐先生？ - 是的 ？
How much is that worth?
那值多少钱？
About 20 million won.
约2000万韩元。
Hi ! It's me, Woo-jin!
你好 ！是我，吴镇！
You have some nerve. You disappear for years, and you come back asking for money.
你还有点神经。你消失了很多年， 然后你回来要钱​​。
Do you think I'm happy to see you?
你觉得我见到你很高兴吗？
- Sorry. - Stopped.
- 对不起。 - 停了。
Come on !
快点 ！
Poor bastard!
可怜的混蛋！
- Sit down. - Yes.
- 坐下。 - 是的。
How did your friend get into debt?
你的朋友是怎么负债的？
He got scammed by Smile Capital.
他被微笑资本骗了。
Smile Capital ? Les types de Gwangan-dong ?
微笑资本？ 广安洞的类型？
I don't know where they are from.
我不知道他们来自哪里。
Whore.
妓女。
Smile Capital is not amateurs.
微笑资本并不是业余爱好者。
It's a big box.
这是一个大盒子。
- How much do you owe them? - One hundred million.
-你欠他们多少钱？ - 一亿。
Whore.
妓女。
You're in trouble.
你有麻烦了。
Exactly, help us.
确切地说，帮助我们。
You're loaded with cash.
你满载现金。
I'll give you a loan at 1% repayable over one year.
我会以 1% 的利率向您提供一年内还款的贷款。
Thank you so much.
太感谢了。
In exchange, come back and work for me.
作为交换，你回来为我工作。
With the pandemic, business is taking off.
疫情之下，生意蒸蒸日上。
You have to take advantage of it to enrich yourself.
你必须利用它来充实自己。
Come back and help me.
回来帮助我。
You will receive a good bonus on each recovery.
每次恢复您都会获得丰厚的奖金。
Damn, you're taking me by surprise.
该死，你让我大吃一惊。
Whore.
妓女。
A year of collecting debts for me.
为我讨债的一年。
I'm offering you an opportunity.
我给你提供一个机会。
You can make golden balls.
你可以制作金球。
You'll never get that much money.
你永远不会得到那么多钱。
I see what you mean, but I wasn't expecting that.
我明白你的意思， 但我没想到会这样。
- Make a decision. - Here we go.
- 做决定。 - 开始了。
Quoi ?
奎伊？
Would that mean beating people up?
是不是就意味着要打人了？
We're not scum.
我们不是人渣。
We are boxers.
我们是拳击手。
Petit.
小。
If you don't pay back Smile Capital, they will kill you and sell your organs.
如果你不还钱，微笑资本 他们就会杀了你，卖掉你的器官。
What are you doing ?
你在干什么 ？
Thank you for everything. I'll come back another time.
谢谢你为我做的一切。 我下次再来。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Are you kidding me ?
你在开玩笑吧 ？
You calm down.
你冷静点。
I'm kidding.
我在开玩笑。
See you next time.
下次见。
Come on, let's go.
来吧，我们走吧。
Whore !
妓女！
Hey, boxer.
嘿，拳击手。
- Stamp here. - All right.
- 在这里盖章。 - 好的。
If business takes off, don't forget our part.
如果业务腾飞， 请不要忘记我们的角色。
Thank you so much.
太感谢了。
- Good job. - Started.
- 好工作。 - 开始了。
- No problem, I hope? - No sir.
- 我希望没问题吧？ - 不，先生。
GOOD. Hold.
好的。抓住。
Money raised today.
今天筹集到的钱。
We collect homeless people's papers all over the city.
我们在全市收集无家可归者的文件。
Who are you ?
你是谁 ？
What do you want ? Get back to work.
你想要什么 ？回去工作。
Pardon.
赦免。
We will do everything to bring you the required amount as soon as possible.
我们将尽一切努力 尽快为您提供所需的金额。
This week ?
本星期 ？
I'll do my best.
我将尽我所能。
KIM JUN-MIN
金俊民
WEARING A MASK MANDATORY
强制佩戴口罩
I didn't keep you waiting too long, I hope.
我希望我没有 让你等太久。
DREAM ON CAPITAL
资本梦想
Why don't you have a mask?
你为什么没有口罩？
I put it.
我把它放了。
I'm not asking you to put it on, but why you took it off.
我不是要求你戴上它， 而是要求你为什么把它脱下来。
We've been waiting for 30 minutes.
我们已经等了30分钟了。
I was suffocating.
我快要窒息了。
You little bastard, you have no patience and you want to be a bodyguard?
你个小混蛋，没有耐心 ，还想当保镖？
Wearing a mask has nothing to do with it!
戴口罩和这个没有什么关系！
Cleared.
清除。
Go away !
离开 ！
Shit.
拉屎。
What a little shit!
真是小事一桩啊！
Whore !
妓女！
- You took off your mask. - No.
- 你摘下了面具。 - 不。
I saw you.
我看见你。
I had lowered it.
我已经把它降低了。
It's the same. Take some responsibility for your mistakes. Out !
一样的。 对你的错误承担一些责任。出去 ！
Go out !
出去 ！
Whore.
妓女。
"Putain" ?
“普坦”？
I'm hallucinating.
我出现幻觉了。
Your mask.
你的面具。
What's your name ?
你叫什么名字 ？
Cheon Dong-woo.
千东宇.
I see. Size ?
我懂了。尺寸 ？
1.87 m. I weigh 74 kg.
1.87米。我体重74公斤。
- Do you do sports ? - Ten years of kickboxing and hapkido.
- 你做运动吗？ - 十年跆拳道和合气道。
- Diploma ? - Security at Yongheon University.
- 文凭 ？ - 龙轩大学的保安。
Hey ! The total !
嘿 ！总数 ！
- The army? - I was exempted.
- 军队？ - 我被豁免了。
Following a sports injury.
运动损伤后。
Too bad.
太糟糕了。
Bye.
再见。
Why are you rejecting me?
你为什么拒绝我？
- I'm looking for a marine. - A marine, obliged?
- 我正在寻找一名海军陆战队员。 - 一名海军陆战队员，有义务吗？
Oui.
哎呀。
Whore. You could have mentioned it in the ad.
妓女。你可以 在广告中提到它。
What, “damn”?
什么，“该死”？
- You wasted my time! - A little respect for your elders.
- 你浪费了我的时间！ - 对长辈有一点尊重。
Fuck you.
去你的。
You just had to not piss off...
你只需要别生气...
You're going to leave now.
你现在要离开了。
All right !
好的 ！
MARINE IF YOU CAN’T GET IT, PERSEVERE!
海军陆战队员 ，如果你做不到，请坚持！
HONG WOO-JIN - 1 216E PROMO
洪宇镇 - 1 216E 宣传片
Come over here.
过来吧。
Why do we run?
我们为什么要跑步？
He's a senior marine!
他是一名高级海军陆战队员！
A single man in Korea can transfer a trillion won
韩国单身男子 可转账万亿韩元
with a single phone call.
只需一个电话。
Bang Seong-ho.
方成浩.
And only one man knows what Mr. Bang looks like.
只有一个人知道 邦先生长什么样。
- And only you know who this man is? - Shut up.
- 只有你知道这个人是谁？ - 住口。
Mr. Bang only ever took one person under his tutelage.
邦先生只师从过 一个人。
M. Choi.
崔先生。
It's thanks to him that I earn my living.
多亏了他，我才能谋生。
Do you see the blackboard ?
你看到黑板了吗？
- Yes.
- 是的。
Good. Alright.
好的。好吧。
Mr. Choi wants to hire someone.
崔先生想雇一个人。
Someone who would be willing to risk their life to save someone.
一个愿意冒着生命危险 去拯救某人的人。
Someone generous.
有人慷慨。
Someone who knows our business.
了解我们业务的人。
Yesterday I started looking for candidates,
昨天我开始 寻找候选人，
but none suited.
但没有一个适合。
It was at this very moment that a young marine called me.
就在这时 ，一位年轻的海军陆战队员给我打电话。
Talk about a coincidence!
谈论一个巧合！
He's a marine too, from a previous class.
他也是一名海军陆战队员， 来自以前的班级。
Those promos?
那些促销？
La 1 207e.
拉 1 207e。
I'm from the 734th class.
我是734班的。
- Did you see ? - It's nice to see !
- 你有没有看到 ？ - 很高兴看到！
I will recommend you to Mr. Choi.
我会把你推荐给崔先生。
- Write down your identity number. - Sir.
- 写下您的身份证号码。 - 先生。
Actually, you were contacted to borrow money.
事实上，有人联系你 借钱。
That's why I refer you to Mr. Choi.
这就是为什么 我建议你去找崔先生。
He is as fierce as a tiger,
他凶猛如虎，
but understanding and generous.
但理解和慷慨。
If he takes a liking to you, he will take care of you like a marine!
如果他喜欢你， 他会像海军陆战队员一样照顾你！
Is he a marine?
他是海军陆战队员吗？
What if he's a marine?
如果他是海军怎么办？
Oui.
哎呀。
He was exempted because he was out of school.
他因失学而获得豁免。
Yes, well, so to speak.
是的，可以这么说。
I said "navy" to mean "cool", like rappers say "hip-hop".
我说“海军蓝”的意思是“酷”， 就像说唱歌手说“嘻哈”一样。
What are you talking about ? Write your ID number.
你在说什么 ？ 写下您的身份证号码。
All right.
好的。
Did you see his face? I think it looks good.
你看到他的脸了吗？ 我觉得看起来不错。
- THANKS. - Let's go.
- 谢谢。 - 我们走吧。
You don't have to thank me.
你不用谢我。
How many were your attackers?
攻击你的人有多少人？
About ten.
大约十个。
- But it was someone else who beat me. - Only one?
- 但打败我的是别人。 - 只有一个？
A real mirror cabinet. He headbutted me.
真正的镜柜。 他用头撞了我。
Hard to dodge, that.
很难躲开，那个。
Say, if ever
说吧，如果有的话
you have to collect debts to pay yours,
你必须追债 来偿还你的债务，
what will you do ?
你会怎么做 ？
We will advise together.
我们将一起提供建议。
Good job, as always. THANKS.
干得好，一如既往。谢谢。
No, we'll take care of it.
不，我们会处理的。
This is Mr. Oh's specialty.
这是Oh先生的专长。
All right.
好的。
We just have to go to Yang-jung's for lunch one of these days. See you soon.
有一天我们必须去杨荣家吃午饭。再见。
Yang Jae-myeong went to Chungjeong-ro and Myeong-dong
梁在明去 了忠正路和明洞
borrow 400 million from seven different loan sharks.
向七个不同的高利贷者借了 4 亿美元。
He gave everything to an executive at Smile Capital in Gwangan-dong.
他把一切都给了 广安洞微笑资本的一位高管。
You know him ?
你认识他吗？
His face doesn't tell me anything.
他的表情没有告诉我任何事情。
He impersonates homeless people to create shell companies
他冒充无家可归者 创建空壳公司
and borrow from loan sharks.
并向高利贷者借钱。
The moneylenders accept,
放债人接受，
because they do not communicate with each other and suspect nothing.
因为他们彼此不沟通 ，也不怀疑任何事情。
They only notice it when they collect the money.
他们只有在收钱时才会注意到这一点。
Whoever designed this plan knows the inner workings of the industry well.
设计这个计划的人都 非常了解行业的内部运作。
It seems that Yang Jae-myeong is just a pawn.
看来 杨在明只是一颗棋子。
How do you know all this?
你怎么知道这一切？
It was in 2001 or 2002.
那是在2001年或2002年。
A fake volunteer at a clinic for the disabled
残疾人诊所的假志愿者
stole their identity papers.
偷走了他们的身份证件。
He created a shell company to take out a loan
他创建了一家空壳公司 来获取贷款
the seven billion won from the moneylenders of Myeong-dong,
明洞放债人的七十亿韩元，
before fleeing to the Philippines.
在逃往菲律宾之前。
A fortune at the time.
当时的一笔财富。
Are we going to let them do it?
我们会让他们这样做吗？
Quoi ?
奎伊？
These loan sharks are being scammed.
这些高利贷者正在被骗。
They're a bit like your colleagues.
他们有点像你的同事。
They will get through this.
他们会渡过难关的。
Loan sharks cannot file a complaint.
高利贷者 不能提出投诉。
Hyeon-ju, it's up to them to sort this out.
贤珠， 这件事得由他们来解决。
I am no longer part of this environment.
我不再是这个环境的一部分。
Not for ten years.
没有十年。
Was the guy who fled to the Philippines caught?
逃到菲律宾的那个人被抓到了吗？
His victims sent henchmen after him in the Philippines.
他的受害者 在菲律宾派出追随者追捕他。
He is dead ?
他死了 ？
It's brutal.
太残酷了。
Hyeon-ju.
贤珠.
I can hire someone to help you.
我可以雇人来帮助你。
Especially not.
尤其不是。
It's dangerous. The proof is that you got hurt.
这很危险。 证据就是你受伤了。
It's just a scratch.
这只是一个划痕。
Anyway.
反正。
I'm more efficient on my own.
我自己一个人效率更高。
Rest.
休息。
Dirty brat!
肮脏的小子！
Nice shot !
好球 ！
Sir, why did you disfigure this young man?
先生， 您为什么要毁容这个年轻人？
Who told you about it?
谁告诉你这件事的？
I asked In-beom.
我问仁范。
Beom talking about all this?
Beom 正在谈论这一切？
- Just me. - Wait, I'm finished.
- 只有我。 - 等等，我说完了。
- Not bad. - Nice shot.
- 不错。 - 好球。
He spat in my face in front of the men.
他当着那些人的面向我脸上吐口水。
I made an example of it.
我举了一个例子。
It makes me extra work.
这让我额外工作。
Jang-do.
张道。
Sometimes you have to take the lead.
有时你必须带头。
Instill fear.
灌输恐惧。
Oui.
哎呀。
This rich kid didn't call me back.
这个富家子弟没有给我回电话。
It has been a week.
已经一周了。
I will arrange a meeting to convince him to support us.
我将安排一次会议 来说服他支持我们。
Alright.
好吧。
APPLICATION FOR THE 38TH BEGINNERS TOURNAMENT
第38届初学者锦标赛报名
Hey, he really has an athletic body.
嘿嘿， 他的身材确实是运动型的。
Weren't you a boxer, too?
你不也是一名拳击手吗？
Not at this level.
还不到这个级别。
This body proves his determination and seriousness.
这身体证明了 他的决心和认真。
Looks don't lie.
外表不会说谎。
It's true.
这是真的。
But he knows nothing about money lending.
但他对放钱一无所知。
Merci.
谢谢。
This is Kim Gun-woo's new friend.
这是金建宇的新朋友。
According to the investigator,
据调查人员称，
he had busted gangsters in Incheon
他在仁川抓获了歹徒
and set out to escape them.
并开始逃离他们。
No more gaps since.
从此不再有间隙。
He worked for loan sharks, he knows the business.
他为高利贷者工作， 他了解生意。
I think it would be good to hire them both.
我认为雇用他们两人会很好。
- Let's start by seeing Gun-woo. - Alright.
- 让我们从见建宇开始吧。 - 好吧。
It's here.
它在这里。
SUSHI
寿司
Bonjour.
你好。
Mr. Moon sent you, right?
是月亮先生派你来的吧？
Oui.
哎呀。
After you.
您先请。
- Go for it. - Me ?
- 大胆试试吧。 - 我 ？
Oui.
哎呀。
Hello, I'm Kim Gun-woo.
大家好，我是金建宇。
Sit down.
坐下。
All right.
好的。
I can refer to you informally ?
我可以非正式地向您介绍一下吗？
Yes sir.
是的先生。
Did you hurt your cheek?
你的脸颊受伤了吗？
Yes, trying to stop loan sharks from trashing my mother's cafe.
是的，试图阻止高利贷者 破坏我母亲的咖啡馆。
I was a loan shark myself.
我自己就是个放高利贷的人。
It's been a while since I stopped.
我停下来已经有一段时间了。
All right.
好的。
Now I offer zero interest loans
现在我提供零息贷款
to pay for the care of sick people.
支付病人的护理费用。
I see.
我懂了。
I have work for you.
我有工作给你。
I'm teaching the ropes to a young person.
我正在向一个年轻人传授诀窍。
All right.
好的。
We are not related.
我们没有关系。
- But I don't have any other family. - I see.
- 但我没有其他家人。 - 我懂了。
I'm afraid that working alone, something will happen to her.
我怕 她一个人干活，会出事。
So I'm looking for someone good to ensure their safety.
所以我正在寻找一个好的人 来确保他们的安全。
- I wouldn't have to recover any money? - No, it's not about that.
- 我不需要追回任何钱吗？ - 不，不是这个。
- You would be a bodyguard. - I see. All right !
- 你会成为一名保镖。 - 我懂了。好的 ！
At the risk of offending you,
冒着冒犯你的风险，
I found out about you.
我发现了你的事。
No, that doesn't offend me at all.
不，这根本不会冒犯我。
Even in difficult times, you showed kindness
即使在困难时期， 你也表现出善意
and determination.
和决心。
Now that I've met you, I see that you have a frank outlook.
现在见到你， 我发现你有一种坦诚的态度。
- You are trustworthy. - THANKS.
- 你是值得信赖的。 - 谢谢。
- Why do you box? - As a child, I wanted to be strong.
- 你为什么打拳击？ - 小时候，我想变得坚强。
For what ?
为了什么 ？
My father never resisted alcohol.
我父亲从来不抵制酒精。
It got complicated when I entered college.
当我进入大学时，情况变得复杂。
He started drinking and hitting my mother.
他开始喝酒并殴打我的母亲。
I was just a kid, it motivated me to become strong.
我还只是个孩子， 它激励我变得坚强。
- Does he live with you? - No.
- 他和你住在一起吗？ - 不。
They divorced, I haven't seen him since I was 16.
他们离婚了， 我从16岁起就没有见过他了。
- I come from the countryside. - I see.
- 我来自农村。 - 我懂了。
My father was a sharecropper.
我的父亲是一名佃农。
I see.
我懂了。
I have a very clear memory of the year I was ten.
我对十岁那年的记忆非常清晰。
There had been a famine and poor harvests.
当时正值饥荒 ，收成不佳。
We couldn't pay our rent,
我们付不起房租，
and the owner sent his men
主人派了他的人
beating my father...
殴打我的父亲...
in front of the whole village.
当着全村人的面。
My father was seriously injured in the head.
我父亲 头部受重伤。
but we didn't have enough to pay for the hospital.
但我们没有 足够的钱支付医院费用。
He died suffering martyrdom.
他殉道而死。
This is what motivated me to become rich.
这就是我致富的动力。
I decided to help people
我决定帮助人们
who do not have the means to care for themselves.
没有能力照顾自己的人。
What I mean,
我的意思是说，
it is that a generous heart can overcome all obstacles.
就是一颗宽容的心 可以克服一切障碍。
Yes, I always try to be generous.
是的，我总是尽量表现得慷慨大方。
You're not a good talker.
你不是一个善于说话的人。
Pardon. Talking is not my strong suit.
赦免。说话不是我的强项。
- Oh no? - Not.
- 不好了？ - 不是。
- Come. - I'm coming.
- 来。 - 我来了。
SO ?
所以 ？
It was, I think.
我想是的。
I mostly let Mr. Choi do the talking.
我主要让崔先生说话。
I told you it would go well!
我告诉过你一切都会很顺利！
You see ?
你看 ？
SO ?
所以 ？
He has no sense of humor.
他没有幽默感。
But he has a good background.
但他有很好的背景。
I see.
我懂了。
Attention.
注意力。
He needs money. Take care of it by tonight.
他需要钱。 今晚之前就照顾好它。
All right.
好的。
- Help me some. Not too much. - Eat well.
- 帮我一些。不是太多。 - 吃好。
- It's not much, but hey. - Madam, I love kimchi stew.
- 虽然不多，但是嘿。 - 女士，我喜欢泡菜炖菜。
I can taste ?
我能尝到吗？
Yes of course.
是的当然。
- Be careful, it's hot. - It's too good. THANKS.
- 小心点，很热。 - 太好了。谢谢。
Enjoy your food.
享受你的食物。
In any case, it's nice of you to help us.
无论如何， 你能帮助我们真是太好了。
It's all natural. Your son is a very good friend.
这一切都很自然。 你儿子是一个非常好的朋友。
And we are marines!
我们是海军陆战队！
Everything will be alright.
一切都会好的。
Merci.
谢谢。
Eat, it'll get cold.
吃吧，会凉的。
- All right ! - Enjoy your food.
- 好的 ！ - 享受你的食物。
Enjoy your food.
享受你的食物。
Who is it ?
是谁 ？
I will see.
我再看看吧。
Yes, can I help you?
是的，我可以帮你吗？
I work for Mr. Choi.
我为崔先生工作。
I see.
我懂了。
Delighted.
高兴极了。
Hold. One hundred million won.
抓住。一亿韩元。
- What ? - Two years of salary in advance.
- 什么 ？ - 预付两年工资。
More...
更多的...
You start tomorrow at 10 a.m.
明天上午 10 点开始。
I will text you the address.
我会把地址发短信给你。
Thank you very much sir.
先生非常感谢您。
Instead, thank Mr. Choi.
相反，要感谢崔先生。
- Yes. - I go.
- 是的。 - 我去。
Thanks again.
再次感谢。
Excellent, this omelette.
太棒了，这个煎蛋卷。
I can do it again.
我可以再做一次。
Who was it ?
他是谁 ？
Hey well...
嘿好吧...
Mom, I didn't tell you,
妈妈，我没有告诉你，
but an acquaintance of Woo-jin found me a job.
但宇进的一个熟人 给我找到了一份工作。
Work ?
工作 ？
Bodyguard for someone in the family of a wealthy businessman.
富商家族的保镖。
I made a good impression.
我给我留下了很好的印象。
He gave me an advance on my salary.
他预支了我的工资。
Cent millions.
分百万。
- Really ? - Yes.
- 真的 ？ - 是的。
Let's start by paying off our debt to prevent it from increasing.
让我们从偿还债务开始， 防止债务增加。
I feel like I'm mortgaging your future.
我觉得 我正在抵押你的未来。
But no, mom.
但不，妈妈。
The main thing is that we are both happy.
最主要 的是我们俩都很开心。
I will continue to train.
我会继续训练。
I will resume boxing after the pandemic. It'll be fine.
疫情过后我会恢复拳击。会没事的。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Smile, mom. It's good news.
微笑吧，妈妈。这是个好消息。
Merci, Woo-jin.
Merci, Woo-jin.
- Good evening. - Pushes you.
- 晚上好。 - 推你。
Come see.
来看看。
Quoi ?
奎伊？
- He's already here. - He's ahead.
- 他已经来了。 - 他领先了。
Is he the son of the CEO of Iil Group?
他是Iil集团CEO的儿子吗？
- You know him ? - My heart.
- 你认识他吗？ - 我的心。
- Beware of him. - For what ?
- 小心他。 - 为了什么 ？
- Say! - I'm coming.
- 说！ - 我来了。
Do you have wipes? I rang the bell, no one answered.
你有湿巾吗？ 我按了门铃，没有人回应。
Sorry, I brought this to you.
抱歉，我把这个带给你了。
When I was manager at Speed, he fought the owner.
当我在 Speed 担任经理时， 他与老板发生争执。
Hyeon-ji ?
贤智？
Oui.
哎呀。
A drunken argument about politics.
关于政治的醉酒争论。
The following week, we were subject to a tax audit.
接下来的一周， 我们接受了税务审计。
She had to sell her house to pay them.
她不得不卖掉自己的房子来支付他们的费用。
Later, we learned that he had friends everywhere.
后来我们才知道 ，他到处都有朋友。
Tax authorities, police, Ministry of Finance... His family is everywhere.
税务机关、警察、财政部…… 他的家人无处不在。
Like all rich people.
和所有有钱人一样。
Really ?
真的 ？
She will have insulted one of her politician cousins.
她会侮辱 她的一位政客表兄弟。
I worry about you.
我很担心你。
Go ahead.
前进。
Did you order girls?
你订的是女孩吗？
He advised us against it.
他建议我们不要这样做。
Good. Do not worry.
好的。不用担心。
He is accompanied.
他有陪伴。
- Who ? - A former member of the academy.
- WHO ？ - 学院前成员。
Is he still a cop?
他还是警察吗？
Yes, he was first in his class.
是的，他是班上的第一名。
Does he know who you are?
他知道你是谁吗？
No. We were several years apart.
不。我们相差好几年。
Whatever happens, don't intervene, understand?
不管发生什么，都 不要插手，明白吗？
Oui.
哎呀。
I'll tell them to call.
我会告诉他们打电话。
Good evening.
晚上好。
Here you are.
给你。
He's a cousin of mine.
他是我的表弟。
Min Gang-yong, delighted.
闵刚勇很高兴。
I like your voice.
我喜欢你的声音。
Kim Myeong-gil.
金明吉.
He mentioned alcohol, so I joined in.
他提到了酒精， 所以我也加入了。
Does it bother you ?
它妨碍到你了吗 ？
It seems you have big plans.
看来你有很大的计划。
- Delighted. - Me too.
- 高兴极了。 - 我也是。
This is Lee Jin-su, an associate of mine.
这是李镇秀，我的同事。
Delighted. I've seen you somewhere before, right?
高兴极了。我 以前在哪里见过你，对吗？
I have an all-purpose face, that's all.
我有一张万能的脸，仅此而已。
- Sit down. - THANKS.
- 坐下。 - 谢谢。
I brought this so I wouldn't drink at your expense.
我带这个来 是为了不让你喝酒。
You should not have.
你不应该。
I serve you ?
我为你服务？
Excuse him, he doesn't drink.
对不起，他不喝酒。
Just one sober person complicates things.
只要一个人清醒， 事情就会变得复杂。
Sharing a drink helps prevent you from changing your mind later.
一起喝一杯 有助于防止你以后改变主意。
So drink his share like a loyal friend. I bet you handle alcohol well.
因此，请像一位忠实的朋友一样喝他的那一份。 我打赌你能很好地处理酒精。
I appreciate loyalty.
我很欣赏忠诚。
Go for a second one.
去买第二个吧。
You drink it like water.
你像喝水一样喝它。
- It's going well, isn't it? - Yes.
- 进展顺利，不是吗？ - 是的。
My turn to serve you.
轮到我为您服务了。
A small glass ?
一个小玻璃杯？
A big glass, you mean.
你是说一个大玻璃杯。
- I'll take this. - GOOD.
- 我要这个。 - 好的。
Hey !
嘿 ！
With my colleagues, we thrive on soju, so if someone offers me good whiskey,
和我的同事们一起，我们靠烧酒而茁壮成长， 所以如果有人给我提供上好的威士忌，
I take advantage of it!
我利用它！
It's up to me to serve you.
由我来为您服务。
What a descent!
这是何等的血统啊！
I want some too. It's my whiskey, after all.
我也想要一些。 毕竟这是我的威士忌。
Non ?
非？
I serve you. I can refer to you informally ?
我为你服务。我可以非正式地向您介绍一下吗？
You go-y.
你走吧。
Trinquons.
特林昆斯。
Hey !
嘿 ！
Come on !
快点 ！
Dry ass!
干屁股！
You have quite a descent.
你很有血统。
Gang-yong, if alcohol makes me do something stupid, stop me.
江勇，如果酒精 让我做蠢事，请阻止我。
If it gets out of hand...
如果事情失控的话...
Where did I put them?
我把它们放在哪里了？
I will arrest someone.
我会逮捕一个人。
Pass your drinks.
把你的饮料递过来。
Whore.
妓女。
Now that we've had a drink together, let's put our cards on the table.
现在我们已经一起喝过一杯了， 让我们把牌摆到桌面上吧。
Alright.
好吧。
You are rich ?
你好有钱 ？
I come from a modest background, I work hard.
我出身卑微， 工作努力。
Do you have 100 billion?
你有1000亿吗？
I never lie when it comes to money.
在金钱方面我从不说谎。
Never ?
绝不 ？
It's strange.
真奇怪。
I was told that even if I looked hard, Smile Capital didn't have 50 billion.
有人告诉我，我再仔细一看， 微笑资本也没有500亿。
It's true.
这是真的。
The tax authorities must not be doing their job well.
税务机关一定没有做好他们的工作。
We call them ?
我们称他们为？
Be careful, you're drunk.
小心点，你喝醉了。
Mr. Kim looks upset, apologize to him.
金先生看起来很不高兴，向他道歉。
Oh sorry.
哦对不起。
I shouldn't have drunk on an empty stomach, the alcohol is going to my head.
我不应该空腹喝酒， 酒精会冲昏头脑。
Don't worry about the money.
别担心钱的事。
Oh no?
不好了？
If you say so.
如果你这么说的话。
I never worry about money.
我从不担心钱。
Hey, my mother asked me to say hello to Mr. Bang.
嘿，妈妈让我 跟邦先生打个招呼。
She thanks him again.
她再次感谢他。
But the man who brought him the money...
但那个给他带来钱的人……
He was already in his forties.
他已经四十多岁了。
It's been 20 years, and you haven't aged. What's your secret?
20年过去了，你还没有老。 你的秘密是什么？
Un lifting ?
取消举升？
It's fashionable.
很时尚。
Did you think I wouldn't tell him about it?
你以为我不会告诉他这件事吗？
Well then?
好吧？
You do not say anything anymore ?
你不再说什么了吗？
Are you the type to shut up as soon as you lose the advantage?
你是那种一旦失去优势就闭嘴的人吗？
Is that what they taught you in prison?
他们在监狱里就是这么教你的吗？
I'm hallucinating, he's laughing.
我出现幻觉了，他在笑。
That's it, smile.
就这样吧，微笑。
Putain, Gang-yong!
Putain, Gang-yong !
I don't want to drink anymore. Let's get this over with.
我不想再喝酒了。让我们结束这一切吧。
Listen, Kim.
听着，金。
I'll put in the 100 billion.
我会投入1000亿。
This is the last time we see each other.
这是我们最后一次见面。
Come on, my little Kim.
来吧，我的小金。
Come on, come here.
来吧，到这里来。
If you attack my family again,
如果你再袭击我的家人
you are dead.
你死了。
Understood ?
明白了吗？
You really lived! You even have a scar.
你真的活过！ 你甚至还有疤痕。
I told you !
我告诉你了 ！
Lets' go.
我们走吧。
Let's go. We stayed too long.
我们走吧。我们呆得太久了。
I tried to give you the benefit of the doubt.
我试图 给你一个无罪推论。
You seemed like a deserving guy.
你看起来是一个值得的人。
Jang-do.
张道。
Oui ?
哎呀？
Take Beom and find me a file on him.
带Beom 给我找一份关于他的档案。
Serious.
严肃的。
Understood.
明白了。
ANTIQUE STORE
古董店
- Thanks for coming. - My pleasure.
- 感谢你的到来。 - 我的荣幸。
What are you doing ?
你在干什么 ？
Quoi ?
奎伊？
- You want to come ? - Yes.
- 你想来吗？ - 是的。
I'll try to convince Mr. Choi to hire me.
我会尽力 说服崔先生雇用我。
- That would be cool, right? - It would be great.
- 那会很酷，对吧？ - 这会很棒。
So support me.
所以支持我。
Throw me some flowers.
扔给我一些花。
- All right. - Okay, let's go.
- 好的。 - 好吧，我们走吧。
- Good morning.
- 早上好。
- Did you find it without any problem? - Yes.
- 你找到它没有任何问题吗？ - 是的。
I just paid off my loans with your money.
我刚刚用你的钱还清了我的贷款 。
Thank you so much.
太感谢了。
You'll do well.
你会做得很好。
I'll do my best.
我将尽我所能。
Hello Sir ! My name is Hong Woo-jin.
你好先生 ！ 我叫洪宇镇。
I used to work for Mr. Moon .
我曾经为Moon先生工作过 。
I'm Gun-woo's brother in arms since the marines.
我从海军陆战队起就是建宇的战友
Oui.
哎呀。
I followed Gun-woo's misadventures from afar .
我远远地注视着 建宇的不幸遭遇。
I wanted to help him, but there was nothing I could do.
我想帮助他， 但我无能为力。
And it was eating away at me.
它正在吞噬我。
I'm relieved that someone good helped him.
有好心人帮助了他，我就放心了。
Thank you.
谢谢。
And I came to the conclusion
我得出结论
that I could be useful to you.
我可以对你有用。
I know the job better.
我更了解这份工作。
It embarrasses me to brag in front of you,
向你夸耀我都不好意思
the living legend of Myeong-dong,
明洞活生生的传奇，
but I know it better than him.
但我比他更清楚。
"What if I accompanied Gun-woo to teach him the trade
“如果我陪建宇 教他这门手艺呢？
"and assist him?
“并协助他？
“That would be useful to him, wouldn’t it?
“这对他来说很有用，不是吗？
“It would even be very beneficial.”
“这甚至会非常有益。”
It is this reasoning that brings me here.
正是这个推理把我带到了这里。
With your permission, I will accompany him to help him!
如果你允许的话， 我就陪他一起去帮助他！
Why not ?
为什么不 ？
Merci !
谢谢！
Sit down.
坐下。
All right.
好的。
- THANKS ! - Thanks for the tea!
- 谢谢 ！ - 谢谢你的茶！
I forgot to mention one detail.
我忘了提及一个细节。
I pay you, but I'm not the one who hires you.
我付钱给你， 但我不是雇用你的人。
Pardon ?
请原谅？
You have an interview with Hyeon-ju.
你接受了贤珠的采访。
I see.
我懂了。
More...
更多的...
What if I don't pass the interview?
如果我没有通过面试怎么办？
You will have to return the salary.
你必须退还工资。
But I used it to repay the loan.
但我用它 来偿还贷款。
I'm sure it will be fine.
我相信一切都会好起来的。
Quoi ?
奎伊？
I'm warning you, Hyeon-ju doesn't want a bodyguard.
我警告你， 贤珠不需要保镖。
But I'm not convincing, Mr. Choi.
但我没有说服力，崔先生。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
M. Choi.
崔先生。
If I can persuade Hyeon-ju to hire Gun-woo and me,
如果我能说服贤珠 雇用我和建宇的话
I will have a salary too?
我也会有工资吗？
That works.
这样可行。
Woo-jin.
宇进.
I have a head massage waiting for me.
我有头部按摩在等着我。
- All right. - Bye.
- 好的。 - 再见。
Bon massage.
邦按摩。
Hold...
抓住...
Take this
拿着它
and treat yourself to a good meal.
并犒赏自己一顿美餐。
All right. Thank you sir.
好的。谢谢你，先生。
This is truly my dream job.
这确实是我梦想的工作。
Sir.
先生。
Both...
两个都...
stick together no matter what.
无论如何都要团结在一起。
All right !
好的 ！
Good luck !
祝你好运 ！
Merci !
谢谢！
Damn then!
那该死！
Holy shit!
天啊！
- What ? - Come !
- 什么 ？ - 来 ！
Quoi ?
奎伊？
- It was in there. - Serious ?
- 就在那里。 - 严肃的 ？
There must be 100 million won.
必须有一亿韩元。
- That much ? - Hold on.
- 那么多 ？ - 坚持，稍等。
Did you see that ?
你看到了吗 ？
Whore ! In there too.
妓女！也在那里。
Attends...
参加...
THERE ARE GUESTS AT THE BOOKSTORE CHAT WELL WITH THEM
书店里有客人 和他们聊得很开心
Piss off.
生气。
Seventeen billion, 18 billion, 19 billion...
170亿、 180亿、190亿……
- 21 billion... - Woo-jin.
- 210亿... - 宇进。
In truth,
事实上，
I already met Hyeon-ju.
我已经认识贤珠了。
What ? How so ?
什么 ？为何如此 ？
On my way to your house the other day,
那天我去你家的路上，
she was chasing a guy dressed as a homeless person.
她正在追一个装扮成无家可归者的人。
I followed her, and she tasered me.
我跟着她， 她电击了我。
- A taser shot? - Yes.
- 泰瑟枪射击？ - 是的。
Did you fight against her?
你跟她吵架了吗？
No, she just insulted me, that's all.
不，她只是侮辱我，仅此而已。
I see.
我懂了。
Do not worry.
不用担心。
I'll take care of everything.
我会处理好一切。
Do not say anything.
不要说什么。
Be discreet.
保持谨慎。
- You made me lose count. - Sorry.
- 你让我数不清了。 - 对不起。
Hello, Hyeon-ju.
你好，贤珠。
We were chosen by Mr. Choi himself
我们是崔先生亲自挑选的
to guarantee your safety at work.
以保证您的工作安全。
Hashtag, bodyguard. Hashtag, close protection.
标签，保镖。 标签，贴身保护。
Hashtag, manager.
标签，经理。
Hashtag, we're here for you.
标签，我们在这里等你。
Can you repeat ?
你可以重复吗 ？
We're here for you. Delighted.
我们随时为您服务。高兴极了。
At your service.
乐意效劳。
We'll do whatever you need.
我们会做你需要的一切。
I do not need anything.
我什么都不需要。
Okay, but in the future, let us know if you need anything.
好的，但是以后 如果您需要什么，请告诉我们。
I won't need anything in the future either, just go.
以后我也不需要什么了，走吧。
Don't you like us?
你不喜欢我们吗？
That's not the question. I don't need you.
这不是问题。 我不需要你。
You can't know until you see us at work.
直到你看到我们在工作时你才会知道。
I do very well on my own,
我自己也做得很好
I really don't need you.
我真的不需要你。
So stop insisting.
所以别再坚持了。
I do not insist...
我不强求...
You see, you start again.
你看，你又开始了。
go away
离开
Mr. Choi said we could stay.
崔先生说我们可以留下来。
Even against my will?
甚至违背我的意愿？
Whore ! And a liar to boot!
妓女！而且还是个骗子！
You're faker than your sneakers.
你比你的运动鞋还假。
Cleared.
清除。
Get out, I said!
出去吧，我说！
Are you deaf or what?
你是聋子还是什么？
Get the fuck out!
他妈的滚出去！
I really need this job.
我真的需要这份工作。
Just for a month.
就一个月。
If I don't make myself useful, I'll leave.
如果我不能让自己变得有用，我就会离开。
Just one month, please.
就一个月吧，拜托。
Stopped.
停了。
If you need money, my grandfather will give you a loan.
如果你需要钱， 我爷爷会给你贷款。
I'll talk to him about it. Come on, go away.
我会和他谈谈这件事。来吧，走开。
That's embarrassing now.
现在就尴尬了
Money...
钱...
Mr. Choi has already given me two years' advance on my salary.
崔先生已经 预支了我两年的工资。
My mother accepted a fraudulent loan from Smile Capital.
我母亲接受了 微笑资本的欺诈性贷款。
She has a debt of 100 million,
她负债1亿，
and I had to pay her back this morning with this money.
今天早上我必须把这 笔钱还给她。
If I have to give it back to him, I'll be in big trouble.
如果我必须把它还给他， 我就有大麻烦了。
Please, I beg you.
拜托我求你了。
Standing.
常设。
Let's go eat.
一起去吃。
Why did you borrow money from them?
你为什么向他们借钱？
My mother was fooled.
我妈妈被骗了。
How much did she borrow?
她借了多少钱？
Cent millions.
分百万。
Was the money enough to calm them down? Was there any other damage?
钱够让他们平静下来吗？ 还有其他损坏吗？
My mother runs a café,
我妈妈经营一家咖啡馆，
but they ransacked it.
但他们洗劫了它。
I see.
我懂了。
Is that where you got your facial injury?
你面部受伤的地方是那里吗？
Oui.
哎呀。
You have to blame them.
你必须责怪他们。
Did you file a complaint?
您投诉了吗？
Non.
非。
They threatened to kill my mother.
他们威胁要杀死我的母亲。
Who ?
WHO ？
Their boss.
他们的老板。
Hot in front, the hamburgers are served!
前面热腾腾的，汉堡包上桌啦！
Listen to me before you eat.
吃之前先听我说。
As you know,
如你所知，
my grandfather is no longer a loan shark.
我的祖父不再是一个高利贷者。
He makes zero interest loans.
他提供零息贷款。
But sometimes,
但是有时，
bastards abuse his generosity.
混蛋滥用他的慷慨。
Including a man named Yang Jae-myeong.
其中包括一个名叫杨在明的人。
He said his mother had to have surgery.
他说他的母亲必须接受​​手术。
He disappeared with ten million.
他带着一千万失踪了。
It took me six months to find him.
我花了六个月才找到他。
I saw him begging in front of the metro.
我看见他在地铁前乞讨。
At first I thought he was really on the street,
起初 我以为他真的是在街上，
but as I passed him, I saw that his teeth were clean.
但当我经过他身边时， 我发现他的牙齿很干净。
So, I followed him.
于是，我就跟着他了。
He and his henchmen pretend to be homeless
他和他的追随者 假装无家可归
to steal the papers of real homeless people.
窃取真正无家可归者的证件。
They open bank accounts in the name of shell companies,
他们以空壳公司的名义开设银行账户，
scam small loan sharks
骗取小额高利贷
and borrow hundreds of millions.
并借了数亿。
Their tactics were too ingenious
他们的战术太巧妙了
so that Yang Jae-myeong thought about it.
让杨在明这么想。
I found out he was close to this man.
我发现 他和这个人很亲近。
You know him ?
你认识他吗？
Oui.
哎呀。
Our goal is to count how many papers they steal in one night.
我们的目标是统计 他们一晚上偷了多少篇论文。
Above all, don't stand out.
最重要的是，不要脱颖而出。
If they spot you,
如果他们发现你，
all my plans are falling through.
我所有的计划都落空了。
ID CARD
身份证
Take a cap, hide your features.
戴上帽子，隐藏你的特征。
Hey, this one?
嘿，这个？
He's dead drunk.
他已经喝醉了。
Maybe he has some stuff on him.
也许他身上有什么东西。
Over there.
在那边。
- Find me one who is sober. - All right.
- 给我找一个清醒的人。 - 好的。
- Follow me. - Yes.
- 跟我来。 - 是的。
- Let's go.
- 我们走吧。
Head down.
低头。
Good day sir.
美好的一天，先生。
Oui.
哎呀。
You should not sleep on the floor on thin newspapers.
你不应该睡在铺有薄报纸的地板 上。
Get something thicker.
买点厚点的。
It's true.
这是真的。
Bon sang.
邦唱歌。
- When was your last meal? - Yesterday or the day before yesterday.
- 你最后一顿饭是什么时候？ - 昨天或前天。
Do not be afraid.
不要害怕。
We represent a homeless association financed by the city.
我们代表一个 由市政府资助的无家可归者协会。
I see.
我懂了。
The municipality created this association so that we can help each other.
市政府创建了这个协会 ，以便我们能够互相帮助。
Do you want to join?
你想要加入吗？
Quoi ?
奎伊？
You won't have to sleep here anymore.
你不必再睡在这里了。
We'll find you a job.
我们会给你找一份工作。
You will have 20 free masks per month.
您每月将有 20 个免费口罩。
And a monthly allowance of 300,000 won.
以及每月30万韩元的津贴 。
300 000 won...
30万韩元...
Sir.
先生。
Do you have papers? We can already register you.
你有论文吗？ 我们已经可以为您注册了。
And we'll bring you the money next week.
下周我们会给你钱。
You understand ?
你明白 ？
- Yes. - GOOD.
- 是的。 - 好的。
Hold.
抓住。
Not a word, places are limited.
不说了，名额有限。
All right.
好的。
Merci.
谢谢。
What a bullshitter.
真是胡说八道。
They already have four...
他们已经有四个...
- Sorry sir. - What ?
- 对不起，先生。 - 什么 ？
We are from a homeless association.
我们来自无家可归者协会。
- And so... - You bastard!
- 所以... - 你这个混蛋！
Bastard! Give me back my ID card!
混蛋！把身份证还给我！
What ? Are you crazy or what? Whore !
什么 ？你是疯了还是怎么的？妓女！
Let me go, asshole!
放开我，混蛋！
No ! We can't intervene!
不 ！我们无法干预！
Subtitles: Pierre Nérisson
字幕：皮埃尔·内里森